Ryan Newnes

Date of birth: 13/08/1994

Nationality: Indian

Gender: Male

E-mail: ryannewnes@pm.me

Phone: +91 8618301167



SOCIAL MEDIA:

A	

itch.io

https://garvbot.itch.io

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

I am an amateur video game developer with some experience using the Unity Game Engine. My biggest strength is web development, I am well versed with front end web technologies and I have about a year of experience with PHP and back end development.

I have also been developing hybrid apps for android and iOS using the Ionic Framework for about four months now.

I am a huge fan of Open Source Software and enjoy reading about cyber security. I also enjoy playing Sports.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:

Qualification	University / board	Year of completion	Grade/ %
B. Sc. in Game Design and	Image College of Arts,	2015 - 18	Pursuing
Development	Animation & Technology		
HSC [12th STD]	St. Vincent's Junior College,	2012	62%
	Pune		
SSC [10th STD]	Delhi Public School, Pune	2010	75%

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

S. No.	Skill	Level of competency
1.	C++	Intermediate
2.	HTML5	Well Versed
3.	JavaScript	Well Versed
4.	Java	Basic
5.	Python	Basic
6.	PHP	Intermediate
7.	MySQL	Basic

SOFTWARE SKILLS:

S. No.	Software	Level of competency
1.	Unreal Development Kit	Basic
2.	Unity 3D	Intermediate
3.	Android Studio	Basic
4.	Blender	Basic
5.	Adobe Photoshop	Intermediate
6.	Adobe Flash	Basic
7.	Ionic Framework	Well Versed

WORK EXPERIENCE:

S. No.	Company	Designation	Projects	Duration
1.	FlippAR	Web Developer	Website and a few	1 Year
	[Bangalore]		games in jQuery and PHP	[March 2018 - March 2019]
2.	Cintero	Software	Client side mobile	3 Months
	Systems	Developer	applications in Ionic	[March 2019 - June 2019]
	[Mumbai]		Framework	

PROJECTS:

S. No.	Project description	Role	Tools used	Link to project
3.	2D Game	Programmer,	Unity Engine	https://drive.google.com/op
	Development	Designer		en?id=1PAVgbSvIv2cT3fVajp
				ZvfcvkXNLzvYa-
4.	Web Game	Programmer,	HTML5 and	https://garybot.itch.io/squirr
		Designer	JavaScript	<u>el-glider</u>
3.	Web-Design	Designer	HTML and CSS	https://www.flippargo.com
	[Internship]			
4.	HTML Quiz	UI and Back end	Javascript, JSON	https://www.flippar.com/ga
	Game	developer	and AJAX	mes/scienceparkquiz/
5.	Tachathan Quiz	Client side ann	Ionic Framework	Not yet released
5.	Techathon Quiz	Client side app		Not yet released
	Game	developer	(Angular	
			Typescript)	

LANGUAGE SKILLS:

S. No.	Language	Level of competency
1.	English	Read, Write & Speak
2.	Hindi	Read, Write & Speak
3.	Marathi	Read & Speak
4.	French	Read & Write

DECLARATION:

I hereby declare that the information provided above is true to the best of $\ensuremath{\mathsf{my}}$ knowledge and belief.

Ryan Newnes (Signature)